 
export const data = [
    {
        questionId: 1,
        question: "What is Next.js?",
        option1: " Open-source JavaScript back-end library",
        option2: " A front-end library to create a database",
        option3: "Next.js is a React-based open-source framework, built for server-side rendered React applications.",
        option4: "None of the mentioned",
        answerText: "The key difference between React and Next.js is the way they handle routing. React uses client-side routing, meaning the page transitions are handled entirely on the client-side using JavaScript." ,
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        questionId: 2,
        question: "The NEXT.JS is based upon ____?",
        option1: "Java",
        option2: "Javascript",
        option3: "React",
        option4: "Python",
        answerText: "The next.js framework is a React-based framework." ,
        answer: 3,
    },  
    {
        questionId: 3,
        question: "For what purpose Next.js is used for ____?",
        option1: "Server-Side Rendering",
        option2: "Client-Side Rendering",
        option3: "Both of the mentioned",
        option4: "None of the mentioned",
        answerText: "The next.js framework is used for the server-side rendering." ,
        answer: 1,
    },  
    {
        questionId: 4,
        question: "Next.js is written in which of the following language?",
        option1: "TypeScript",
        option2: "Javascript",
        option3: "Rust",
        option4: "All the above",
        answerText: "The next.js framework is written in JavaScript, TypeScript, and Rust." ,
        answer: 4,
    },  
    {
        questionId: 5,
        question: "In Next.js, we can quickly edit the top section of each react page by using the built-in ____ react component?",
        option1: "Metadata",
        option2: "Head",
        option3: "Top",
        option4: "All the above",
        answerText: "In Next.js, we can quickly edit the top section of each react page by using the built-in head react component." ,
        answer: 2,
    },  
    {
        questionId: 6,
        question: "How many types of pre-rendering are supported by Next.js?",
        option1: "1",
        option2: "2",
        option3: "3",
        option4: "4",
        answerText: " In Next.js, two types of pre-rendering are supported:\nStatic Generation\nServer-Side Generation" ,
        answer: 2,
    },  
    {
        questionId: 7,
        question: "Which of the following method is used to get data and deliver it as page props so that the page may render based on the props given?",
        option1: "Getprops",
        option2: "Getstatic",
        option3: "Getdynamicprops",
        option4: "getStaticProps",
        answerText: "getStaticProps method is used to get data and deliver it as page props so that the page may render based on the props given." ,
        answer: 4,
    },  
    {
        questionId: 8,
        question: "getStaticProps() function runs at ____.",
        option1: "A - Runtime",
        option2: "B - Compile time",
        option3: "C - Build time",
        option4: "Both A and B",
        answerText: "getStaticProps() function runs at build time." ,
        answer: 3,
    },  
    {
        questionId: 9,
        question: "Which of the following is correct about prop in react?",
        option1: "Can be changed inside another component",
        option2: "Can be changed inside the component",
        option3: " Cannot be changed in the component",
        option4: "All of mentioned",
        answerText: "Props cannot be changed, they are immutable. A prop is a special keyword, that stands for properties." ,
        answer: 3,
    },  
    {
        questionId: 10,
        question: "Using the ____ component, Next.JS allows you to link sites on the client side.",
        option1: "Page Link",
        option2: "Link React",
        option3: "linking",
        option4: "PropTypes",
        answerText: "Using the Link react component, Next.JS allows you to link sites on the client side." ,
        answer: 2,
    },  
]